{
    "id": "c7604423b40343989c01586d381ed5d6",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "John won the first prize. / The first prize .................. by John.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won",
                "was won",
                "has won",
                "had won"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They have appointed them as their monitor. / He ....................... their monitor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has appointed",
                "has been appointed",
                "have been appointed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She has written two books. / Two books .................. by her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are written",
                "have been written",
                "have written"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I sent the parcel in the morning. / The parcel .......................... in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was sent",
                "had been sent",
                "has been sent"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They made the boy drink the milk. / The boy .................. to drink the milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has made",
                "was made",
                "had been made"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They asked him to wait. / He ........................ to wait.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has asked",
                "had asked",
                "was asked"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They have invited me to their party. / I ..................... to their party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have invited",
                "have been invited",
                "had been invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They have called off their wedding. / Their wedding ................. called off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Positive hydrogen atoms attract negative oxygen atoms. / Negative hydrogen atoms ...................... to positive hydrogen atoms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "attracted",
                "are attracted",
                "have attracted"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They took the child to the doctor. / The child ...................... to the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "has taken",
                "had taken",
                "was taken"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The abductors tortured the boy. / The boy ...................... by the abductors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has tortured",
                "was tortured",
                "had tortured"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They hanged the criminal. / The criminal ...................... by them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has hanged",
                "was hanged",
                "had hanged"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The masons are building the house. / The house ........................ by the masons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is built",
                "is being built",
                "has been building"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}